A Guide to the Papers of James M. Goode, 1964-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of James M. Goode 1964-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-22/1/1.801, RG-22/1/1.852
This collection consists of 12 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift of James M. Goode, 2039 new Hampshire Avenue, N.W., Washington, D.C. on 1985 October 10.
Scope and Content Information
The papers consist of notebooks and reports of University of Virginia graduate student, James M. Goode. The history courses taken, with their corresponding professors, include:
History of the Old South, 1790-1860, Paul Gaston; Medieval Civilization, Everett Crosby; The New South, 1865-1960, Paul Gaston; U.S. Diplomatic History, Edward Younger; and, U.S. Intellectual and Cultural History, Merrill Peterson.
U.S. Diplomatic History, taught by Professor Edward Younger; U.S. Intellectual and Cultural History, taught by Professor Merrill Peterson; and, Medieval Civilization, taught by Professor Everett Crosby.
Contents List
- Papers of James M. Goode--paperwork 1964-1966 (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 103, U.S. Intellectual and Cultural History taught by Merrill Peterson 1964 Sep-1965 Jan, n.d., (2 folders) (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 104, U.S. Intellectual and Cultural History taught by Merrill Peterson 1965 Feb-May (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 111, Medieval Civilization taught by Everett Crosby 1965 Jun-Aug (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 112, Medieval Civilization taught by Everett Crosby 1965 Jun-Aug (Box 1)
- Paper, "An Analysis of the Charter of Roger of Valognes, C. 1140," written for Medieval Civilization taught by Everett Crosby 1965 Jul 12 (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 145, U.S. Diplomatic History taught by Edward Younger 1964 Sept-1965 Jan (Box 1)
- Reports: Clayton-Bulwer Treaty; Review and Criticism of The Tragedy of American Diplomacy by William A. Williams; Book Report #1 1964 Nov-1965 May (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 146, U.D. Diplomatic History taught by Edward Younger 1965 Feb-May (Box 1)
- Notebook for History 147, Representative Americans taught by Bernard Mayo 1964 Sep-1965 Jan (Box 2)
- Notebook for History 148, Representative Americans taught by Bernard Mayo 1965 Feb-May, (2 folders) (Box 2)
- Notebook for History 155, History of the Old South, 1790-1860 taught by Paul Gaston 1965 Sep-1966 Jan (Box 2)
- Notebook for History 156, The New South, 1865-1960 taught by Paul Gaston 1966-Feb-May (Box 2)